Everything will change.
Jumanji: The Next Level is a adventure, comedy,
fantasy film directed by Jake Kasdan.
As the gang return to Jumanji to rescue one of their own,
they discover that nothing is as they expect.
The players will have to brave parts unknown and unexplored in
order to escape the world’s most dangerous game.
Dr. Smolder Bravestone, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Franklin 'Mouse' Finbar, played by Kevin Hart.
Professor Sheldon 'Shelly' Oberon, played by Jack Black.
Ruby Roundhouse, played by Karen Gillan.
Ming, played by Awkwafina.
Jefferson 'Seaplane' McDonough, played by Nick Jonas.
Jumanji: The Next Level is a 2019 American action-adventure comedy film directed by Jake
Kasdan, who co-wrote the script with Jeff Pinkner and Scott Rosenberg.
The film is the fourth in the Jumanji film series and a
sequel to Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle (2017).
Dwayne Johnson, Jack Black, Kevin Hart, Karen Gillan, Nick Jonas, Alex Wolff, Morgan Turner, Ser'Darius Blain and Madison
Iseman reprise their roles from the previous film while Awkwafina, Danny Glover, and Danny DeVito join the cast.
The film's plot takes place two years after Welcome to the Jungle, in which the same group of teenagers,
along with an old friend and two unwitting additions, become trapped in Jumanji once again.
There, they all find themselves facing new problems and challenges with both old and
new avatars, while having to save the land from a new villain to escape.
Principal photography took place between January 21 and May 11, 2019, in
locations including Atlanta, New Mexico, Alberta, and Hawaii.
Jumanji: The Next Level was released in the United States on
December 13, 2019, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed $802 million against a
$125–132 million budget, becoming the tenth-highest-grossing film of 2019.
A sequel is due to be released on December 11, 2026.
The film explores themes of magic, animal attack,
body-swap, adventurer, superhuman strength.
The tone is lighthearted.